gamewinners.com 2003-12-02

# Game Winners - Privacy Policy

**Search**  
· [_CHEATS, FAQs_](http://www.gamewinners.com/search.html)  
· [_GAME BOOKS_](http://www.gamewinners.com/books/index.html)  
· [_GAME STORES_](http://www.gamewinners.com/prices.html)  

* * *

**Consoles**  
· [_GAMECUBE_](http://www.gamewinners.com/gamecube/index.html)  
· [_XBOX_](http://www.gamewinners.com/xbox/index.html)  
· [_PLAYSTATION2_](http://www.gamewinners.com/playstation2/index.html)  
· [_PLAYSTATION_](http://www.gamewinners.com/playstation/index.html)  
· [_DREAMCAST_](http://www.gamewinners.com/DC/index.html)  
· [_NINTENDO 64_](http://www.gamewinners.com/n64/index.html)  
· [_SNES_](http://www.gamewinners.com/snes/index.html)  
· [_GENESIS_](http://www.gamewinners.com/GEN/index.html)  
· [_NES_](http://www.gamewinners.com/nes/index.html)  
· [_19 more systems..._](http://www.gamewinners.com/noframes.htm)  
  
**Computers**  
· [_DOS/WINDOWS PC_](http://www.gamewinners.com/DOSWIN/index.html)  
· [_MACINTOSH_](http://www.gamewinners.com/MAC/index.html)  
· [_4 more systems..._](http://www.gamewinners.com/noframes.htm)  
  
**Portables**  
· [_GAME BOY ADVANCE_](http://www.gamewinners.com/game_boy_advance/index.html)  
· [_GAME BOY COLOR_](http://www.gamewinners.com/game_boy_color/index.html)  
· [_GAME BOY_](http://www.gamewinners.com/game_boy/index.html)  
· [_NEO*GEO POCKET_](http://www.gamewinners.com/NGP/index.html)  
· [_7 more systems..._](http://www.gamewinners.com/noframes.htm)  
  
**Other**  
· [_ARCADE_](http://www.gamewinners.com/arcade/index.html)  
· [_DVD VIDEO_](http://www.gamewinners.com/dvd/index.html)  
· [_HANDHELDS_](http://www.gamewinners.com/handheld/index.html)  
  
**Extras**  
· [_GAMESHARK_](http://vgstrategies.about.com/library/gs/bl_gsmain.htm)  
· [_GAME GENIE_](http://www.gamewinners.com/gamegenie.php?game=bl_ggnmain.htm)  
· [_SAVED GAMES_](http://vgstrategies.about.com/library/save/bl_savemain.htm)  

* * *

**Features**  
· [_HOME_](http://www.gamewinners.com/index.html)  
· [_GAME NEWS_](http://www.gamewinners.com/news.html)  
· [_MESSAGE BOARDS_](http://www.gamewinners.com/forums.html)  
· [_CHAT_](http://vgstrategies.about.com/mpchat.htm)  
· [_FREE NEWSLETTER_](http://www.gamewinners.com/newsletter.html)  
· [_SUBMIT A CHEAT_](http://www.gamewinners.com/submit.html)  
· [_TELL A FRIEND_](http://www.gamewinners.com/cgibin/r/recommend.cgi)  

* * *

**More...**  

**Privacy Statement**  

**Game Winners respects your privacy and use of the web.**

Usage information may be analyzed in order to evaluate our system's performance. Your computer reaches us via a particular IP (Internet Protocol) address. This can reveal the identity of your Internet Service Provider, and their local point-of-presence. This data is compiled into statistics to show the server load and reveal peak usage. None of this information is sold or disseminated to outside parties. 

The individual web pages from Game Winners that are requested by your browser are recorded in a server log to allow evaluation of our most popular pages, and to reveal the presence of broken links and other request problems. None of this information is sold or disseminated to outside parties. 

Your browser has the ability to use so-called "cookies" which, unless you disable their use, store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to various web sites. Game Winners does not use cookies on our content. However, banner ads displayed through our advertising broker may elect to use cookies to prevent the same ad being displayed too many times to the same user, or to identify Game Winners as the site responsible for a "click-through" for an advertiser. However, cookies can not reveal any personal information about you. None of this information is available to Game Winners, and therefore is not sold or disseminated to outside parties. 

Game Winners works with third parties that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how these companies manage the privacy of information with serving ads on this site, please go to the following links. 

> Our primary ad delivery solution is through eUniverse. You may review their privacy policy at:  
>  <http://www.euniverse.com/privacy.cfm>. 
> 
> Game Winners, uses the services of Adtegrity.com, LLC for the serving and/or targeting of ads, promotions and other marketing messages. To learn more about Adtegrity.com, including your ability to opt out of their ad system, go to:  
>  <http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp>. 
> 
> Game Winners uses Gorilla Nation, DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here:  
>  <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>
> 
> Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party ad server, Gorilla Nation, Double Click or their affiliates, or individual advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser 

Some services, such as our Chat Room, are provided through our relationship with the Video Game Strategies site at About.com. Privacy information specific to those features may be found at:  
<http://home.about.com/gi/pages/privacy.htm>. 

Any questions regarding the privacy policy may be directed to [webmaster@gamewinners.com](mailto:webmaster@gamewinners.com). 

* * *

**Game Winners was awarded a 4-Star privacy rating from Enonymous.com**[](http://www.privacyratings.org/4starsites.htm)

> "Congratulations. Your site has been awarded an independent 4-star privacy rating from enonymous.com. Enonymous.com conducts independent reviews of web site privacy policies, and this message is to notify you that your domain has recently been rated by one of our privacy analysts. Our 4-star rating system uses objective criteria to assess posted privacy policies, described in detail at http://www.privacyratings.org... 
> 
> Only 3.5% of the 30,000 sites we have reviewed qualify as 4-star sites, meaning they either collect no visitor information, or use it only for direct contact with the explicit permission of visitors. In our analysis, this is an excellent privacy policy, and we invite you to participate in our free 4-star "best privacy" seal program..."   
  
---|---
